Hey, what's going on guys?
It is John here,
and I'm gonna make this quick tutorial for a member,
a recent member to Azer X.
Um, he wanted to recreate this, um, carousel
that we have on, on my video production website.
And so we don't have an exact like template for that,
but I'm gonna show you kind of a workaround
of creating something similar to that if you have the, uh,
all access bundle.
So, you know, we've got the carousel, we've got the, uh,
the iPhone, and we've got a video playing on the inside.
So this is pretty straightforward, pretty easy to make, um,
because there's a lot of processing.
It will take a little second to like render.
But let me just start it from scratch.
I have a 16 by nine sequence here
and I'm gonna type in Carousel
and I'm actually gonna do 16 by nine, sorry, 16 by nine.
And so we have two of these carousels.
We have, um, one where it's not like flat
and I'll show you both options, but it doesn't matter.
Here we go. And so
we have this version right here,
which is the original that I just used.
And we have this version, which kind of, um, the,
the product is facing the front, right?
And then the product titles are underneath it as well.
So to basically recreate that, look,
I need another template.
So inside here, normally you would place like, you know,
an image or yeah, probably like a product, product shot.
Um, I'm gonna go and create a new element here.
I'm gonna type in iPhone.
And we have this really cool like 3D looking iPhone.
So I'm gonna drop that into my timeline like this.
I'm just gonna expand my screen a little bit more.
So I've got my, uh, my iPhone
and I've got an ad over here that's already, um,
let's say it's a sequence.
I can just drag this sequence in here.
So I'm gonna take that sequence
and I'm just gonna drag it into my iPhone template.
And from here, boom, I've got my iPhone with an ad inside
of it, which is kind of cool.
I'm not gonna bother and make any adjustments to this just
for the sake of the tutorial.
But from here I'm actually going to make a subsequence out
of it so that I have this isolated
and you can see it over here now.
Um, so I can go in here
and like change anything if I wanted
to, but I'm not gonna do that.
So from here I'm gonna go back
to my product carousel template.
And in this template it's kind of cool
'cause you can choose how many products you want to rotate.
In this instance I'm gonna keep six.
Um, here you have animation, the distance, um, you know,
I can keep it a little shorter
or closer together, uh, the scale, which is, you know,
you can play with all these features
and all these, uh, settings however way you want.
But here in the product placeholders,
I'm gonna actually drag my subsequence into here.
So let's say you wanted six different styles.
You would go in there and create six different versions
of this iPhone ad.
But for this example, I'm just gonna keep it really simple.
So I'm just gonna drag these all into the product
placeholders
and just like that.
And you're dealing with a lot of stuff here, so you know,
you've got like Moger on Moger,
so you're gonna it just let it kind of respond to
your, your, your Mac or your pc.
But here we go. So now you can see the
actual animation here.
Um, and if you want to like strip this whole thing
of all the, you know, the titles
and whatnot, just go in there
and you can just pretty much delete or you can on
and off the text fill here.
Um, you know, just kind of set everything to zero
or delete anything right here.
Delete that, delete stroke or like on and off stroke.
Um, the text here, I'm gonna remove that
and logo, I'm gonna remove that as well.
And then if I wanted to, I could even like remove the
background entirely so then it's a completely transparent,
uh, carousel.
So yeah, pretty much that's all you have to do.
And then you can render this out, uh,
and place it somewhere else.
I would recommend, you know, rendering it out to an MP four
and then like using that element in another, in, in an ad
or whatever you wanted to use it in.
Um, just for the sake of like efficiency, just
so it like would process faster.
But that's pretty much it guys.
Uh, if you have any questions about it,
I'll just play it back for you one
more time 'cause I rendered it.
Um, there you have it.
Cool little uh, product carousel
and you can do this with a ton of different things.
So if you guys have any requests, any template requests
or template tutorial requests, feel free to reach out
to me, drop it in the channel.
Uh, that's pretty much it guys.
Thank you so much for watching and I hope you guys are
enjoying the templates.